<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?> 
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="faq.xsl" ?> 
<FAQ> 
<s> 
<question>I dont get enough traffic. What do I have to do?</question> 
<answer>You have to do the work actively in order to attract visitors to come and visit your content. They will not find you on their own.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>How do I come up with content ideas for things to post about?</question> 
<answer>You need new content in order to build the archives of your blog and to attract an audience. Creating and publishing new posts is one of your main tasks as a blogger and something that you should prioritize.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>I dont know how to code can I still be a blogger?</question> 
<answer>This is one of the beauties of being a blogger. You can start today without any coding skills or any tech knowledge.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>Which social media platforms should I be active on for my blog?</question> 
<answer>This depends on what type of audience you are trying to attract. You should not be active on all the platforms there are out there.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>Nobody wants to share my content on social media</question> 
<answer>It’s very difficult to get social media shares when you’re just starting out. You need to put in the effort to provide a lot of value to people.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>Nobody follows me on social media. How do I get followers and page likes?</question> 
<answer>You need to ask yourself what value are you providing in your social media presence and what the main reason should be for someone to follow you and take note of you. When you have that sorted, you just cannot wait for people to find you first. You need to go find them yourself.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>What should I name my blog and how do I get a domain name?</question> 
<answer>There are many strategies for picking a name for your blog. You simply need to spend some time thinking about it and getting creative. One simple solution is calling the blog by your own name. Many have been successful with this approach.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>I dont have money. How do I get started?</question> 
<answer>This is one of the beauties of blogging. You can start in few minutes without needing to spend any money at all. Even if you want to do podcasting and video blogging, you dont need any more equipment than the technology you have inside your smartphone.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>I dont have any specific expertise. What should I create content about?</question> 
<answer>You need to dig deeper and find what makes you special and different. What is it that you spend many of your hours on? What is it that you enjoy doing in your free time?</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>There are so many blogs out there, how can I stand out?</question> 
<answer>The answer to this question is all about you. You are unique, you are different from everyone else. You need to put more of yourself into your content and into your blogging presence in general.</answer>
</s> 
<s> 
<question>Should I write in the English language or my mother tongue?</question> 
<answer>yourself what you are trying to achieve. Writing in English gives you access to a larger audience than if you’re writing in any other single language.</answer>
</s> 
</FAQ> 